

SUMMARY

Software engineer with full stack development experience including requirements gathering, design, coding, testing, and demonstrations. Patient mentor with a strong leadership drive who can use communication to achieve team goals. Always willing and excited to take ownership of teams and products to drive them towards success.

EXPERIENCE

Senior Software Engineer, Infor

St. Paul, MN — 2011-present

- Create web based, cloud deployed, ERP user interfaces using JavaScript, Node, jQuery, HTML5, and CSS in an agile environment.
- Senior developer on a team of associate and general level engineers.
- Certified mentor of four engineers.
- Responsible for the design and implementation of new features with a focus on speed, design, usability, and customer needs.
- Point of contact for multiple products used worldwide by hundreds of thousands of users.
- Work directly with customers to solve high priority issues.
- Give new feature presentations and live demos in front of hundreds of customers.
- Develop blog posts and videos to promote and bring excitement to products

Software Engineer, Quantum Retail Technology

Minneapolis, MN — 2011

 Developed supply chain management software using Java and an array of web technologies in an agile/scrum environment.

Quality Assurance Engineer, Winona State University Software Testing and Development Lab

Winona, MN — 2010-2011

- Created a full coverage test plan to be used by future engineers.
- Searched for flaws in various software and report them using bug reporting software.

Teaching Assistant/Personal Tutor, Winona State University

Winona, MN — 2010-2011

• Met with individual students outside of class for additional assistance with problems, labs, or general topic understanding and assisted professors with weekly in-class labs.



EDUCATION

Winona State University, BS Computer Science

Winona, MN — Graduated May 2011

Relevant Courses

- Algorithms and Problem Solving
- Computer and Network Security
- Object Oriented Design
- Software Engineering
- Web Programming

Accomplishments

- Dean's list five consecutive semesters
- Represented computer science department at admitted students' ceremony

SKILLS

Technical

- Languages: JavaScript, CSS, HTML5, PHP, MySQL, XSLT, Java
- Tools used professionally: Node.js, Express, jQuery, Grunt, Babel
- Tools used personally: React, Angular, Webpack, Underscore/Lodash
- Object-oriented software design and development using scrum/agile methods
- Software testing and bug reporting

Personal

- Strong communication skills
- Persistent
- Self-motivated
- Problem solver
- Patient

HOBBIES

- Toastmasters International [Vice President of St. Paul public club 7507]
- Personal programming projects, I enjoy keeping up on the latest frameworks [samples available upon request]
- Woodworking [www.thirdstallwoodworking.com; demonstrates technical writing ability]
- Reading
- Outdoor activities including cycling, golf, hiking, hunting, camping, fishing, and canoeing

REFERENCES

Available upon request

14274 Bloomfield Ct. Rosemount, MN 55068

T: 507.402.6246 E: andy@awbuboltz.com